Next notice
Good afternoon.
We are in Nagoya
We are here in Nagoya.
What are we doing here today?
Seino
Let's go on a date tour and see what we eat!
in Aichi
Bon appétit!
Since we are in Nagoya today
Don't you want to eat something delicious?
Yes, I want to eat!
So, I'm going to ask a certain person
I'll ask a certain person to recommend something for you.
Here you go.
Please come in.
Hello.
This is my aunt.
Yes.
It's nice to meet you.
Thank you.
I'm so happy to hear from you!
What kind of food do you recommend in Nagoya?
A Chinese restaurant in the sacred ground of the Chunichi Dragons.
Oh, I see.
Let me introduce HIKAKIN
Chinese food
The recommended menu is
Stir-fried Robot Shredded Meat and
the other one is very delicious braised radish and white meat
Oh!
Nice.
I wonder what it is?
I can't imagine what it's like.
But you like baseball, don't you, Kuromi?
ChunichiCentral Japan
Chunichi Dragon
Not exactly, but I'm rooting for them.
No, but I like all the teams.
I'm kind of looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to seeing the players' autographs.
I knew it!
Yay!
So many autographs!
I'm going to put those autographs in my eyes and eat some good food.
I'm going to do my best from tomorrow.
Let's go.
I'm off!
HIKAKIN's exquisite gourmet food!
I'm here in Nagoya for the tour.
Let's go eat HIKAKIN's exquisite gourmet food!
It's done!
So cool!
I'm off!
Nagoya!
I'm off to Nagoya!
By the way, you two...
Do you have any favorite food in Nagoya?
Tangi
Oh, I know Tangi!
I know it.
They always put it on our tours.
That's true.
Most of the time, the top is gone, and it's just rice.
I know, I know.
I know what they do at the "What's Up, What's Up, What's Up?
Only the top is left.
Who are you taking?
Who's left?
Who?Who?
Who's there?
Uh, uh...
I'm here.
Yes, sir.
It's ready!
Here you go.
So cute!
That's great!
Ta-da!
Look at that!
Pikaichi
Picayichi, picayichi, picayichi
Pika pika pika
Okay, let's get to it.
Here you go.
I'd like to eat.
I'm hungry.
Let's go.
Okay.
Thank you for watching.
So many signatures.
Wow!
I'd like to sign our autographs, too.
But I might be told that only baseball players are allowed to sign our autographs.
It looks so big!
And shrimp! I'll have to bring Kaki.
Oh, you like shrimp?
Kaki, I like shrimp.
I'm with you! I've got to get Hazuki.
You like shrimp?
I hate shrimp.
Mr. Hazuki doesn't like seafood.
You're not good at that?Aren't you good at saying no?
Then I'd like to place my order right away.
Yes, sir.
Stir-fried burdock root and shredded meat.
Braised radish and white meat, please.
Yes, please.
Burdock root and radish is a very popular dish that we always recommend.
This squid and kuchiri
stir-fried with vegetables
Looks delicious!
Ikakuchi is a rare dish!
Squid tong too?
It's a beak!
When you pull out the leg, you'll find a beak!
It's right there!
There's a round prick through it.
Is this it?
Come on!
Can I?
Yes, please.
I'm so excited!
Fried rice with egg is very popular among young people these days.
It's very popular.
Yes, I'd like that.
Yes, please.
There's the baseball mascot.
Mr. Doala.
Even I know that Doala.
Doala.
She's cute.
Doala wasn't feeling well the other day.
Is that possible?
Not often.
Thank you for watching.
I love you, don't you?
I took the bullet train all the way to Nagoya today.I've been on the bullet train all the way to Nagoya today.
I was reading a thick Major League Baseball dictionary.
I came here to make my studies come true.
I like professional baseball very much.
I watch a lot.
If you have any connection with Mr. Geitz, please let me know.
Well, I'm from Nagoya, so...
I like the Dragons and their players.
We've been around for about 60 years if I'm not mistaken.
My father was a good friend of manager Hoshino.
It's been going on for a long time.
So basically, people who like baseball
There are a lot of baseball fans who come here.
Wow!
Wow! Nami is amazing!
I'd like to season it with something.
Wow! It smells like sesame oil.
Wow! That's great!
Mixing and seasoning
Wow! Wow!
Crispy
Crispy sauce!
Wow! Looks delicious!
Yes, doesn't it look good?
Almost everyone orders
Bon appétit!
Oh, wow.
Is it a popular menu?
It's the most popular.
Most popular?
Wow!
Ta-da!
Kakicha!
Look! Look at the shine!
The luster!Luster!
Amazing!
Finished!
Sparkling!
Shiny!
It's the luster of salt.
It's like this!
Wow! Delicious!
This mouth is this round, deep-fried
It's a round, deep-fried, doughy thing.
Oh, yeah!
That's amazing!
I love them!
Wow!
Thank you!
Sey!
Bon appétit!
You could spin this around, couldn't you?
Yes! Just spin it around.
We'll eat as much as we want.
Spin, spin, spin.
Sure, sure, sure.
I'll have some fried rice, then.
Mr. Frog, I don't have anything.
I'll have the sweet-and-sour pork.
No, I mean...
I'll have the fried rice.
Squid dumplings.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Good, good, good.
I'm off.
Bon appétit.
Bon appétit.Bon appétit!
Wow! Everyone has so many different things.
So many different things.
Oh! Yum!
Yum!
Yum! Yum!
Ah! Yum!
Yum!
Mmm! It's so good!
Wow! Squid is so good!
Mmmm!
It's like Chinese food!
It's really delicious with a lot of flavor!
Delicious!
Mmm!
Amazing!
Melt in your mouth!
Crispy!
Squid is so good!
Oh! Is this good too?
This is great!
Fried rice is also good!
This is the kind you can't stop chopsticks.
Yum!
Wow!
Bon appétit!
So soft and fluffy!
Eggs
Fried rice
Thank you for the food!
Bon appétit!
So cute!
It's so delicious, isn't it?It's so good, isn't it?
Oh, my God.
So fluffy.
I mean, there's usually an egg in fried rice, right?
It's like you can taste three times the fluffiness.
I see. I think I got the message.
I wonder if he really got it.
It's so delicious. It's so rich.
It's not so much the taste, it's the flavor.
Really? Eat it!
I learned it from Kaede's family. Thank you for this.
Thank you very much. They are watching over us.
Look at this. How can a radish be this thin? Amazing.
Mmm!
Unh!
Ew!
Delicious! I don't know.
Garlic?
Yeah, you'll know when you taste it.
Oh, it's so good!
I could go on and on with this one.
The secret ingredient is garlic.
Yes, that's right.
Delicious!
Amazing!
Daikon radish is good.
They're good.
You have a great expression on your face.
Can you taste the garlic? In the back.
You can taste it, too.
It's not too strong, is it?
Yes, it is.
It's amazing.
Garlic is delicious.Garlic is delicious.
I love it. I really love it.
I mean, if it's power before a concert or something...
It's true.
I might get a little weedy.
You know that investment you made the other day?
Wasn't that a little harsh?
It was tough.
When I thought about doing that under the sun...
I thought, "Oh, this could be bad.
It could be bad.
It might be tough.
You have to build up your stamina.
I don't know why, even though we've been touring for a long time.
I felt like I was losing strength.
I thought of a great combination.
Squid over egg fried rice is really good.
What?
It's delicious over this.
Delicious! It's absolutely delicious!
Let's try it.
Try it.
Wow, it's like a sauce.
It's absolutely delicious.
It's good.
Bon appétit.
Wow.
That's good.
Something, something, something...
Something... something... something...
something... something...
something... something... something...
something, something
something nice
something with an "ooh" soundthick starchy sauce made of kuzu or katakuriko flour
white pork
Special fried rice
It's finished!
Special fried rice.
Now that Nogizaka Cafe is open
It reminds me of the menu I came up with.
Oh!
Oh, it's absolutely delicious!
Bon appétit!
Sounds great!
Ha-ha-ha.
What? I won't tell my father.
essee.
Tomo.
-Collapse.
It crumbles.
It looks good
-It looks good
It looks good.
Oh!
It looks good, doesn't it?
Okay, let's all go out at once.
Let's see what you liked best.
I'll point to it.
Have you decided?
I've decided.
Okay, then.
Let's all go out at once.
Yes!
Wow! Wow!
The best!
No, but it's the best by itself.
but it's the combination!
It really is!
It really is!Really!
You can't decide on the best anymore, these girls.
Please order four!
I want you to eat them in combination!
A new way to eat!
This is amazing!
No, it's really good!
Oh no, really Nash
Numb, numb, numb.
Oh, no!
Come on. Come on.
How's it going? You feel a little better?
A little bit.
Oh, shit.
It's really my right leg.
I'm thinking of going to another one.
Can you recommend one?
I'd like to go to "Suzume Odori" in Kobe, which is out of "Ikkojiyo".
Oh, Kobe Koro!
What do you recommend, Suzume Odori?
Oh, it's dessert!
This time of year, I recommend shaved ice with bracken rice cakes!
Wow, straw rice cakes?
Strawberry cakes?
I'm going on tour north of Nagoya, and I'm going to walk on Suzume Odori's shaved ice!
I'm off to enjoy the shaved ice with warabimochi!
Excuse me, excuse me.
May I have your autograph to commemorate your visit today?
Can I have your autograph?
Here.
Thank you. Here.
Thank you very much.
I'd like to sign our autographs, too.
They might say no baseball players.
They bought it.
They're going to put it on display.They are going to decorate it.
Come and see this one too!
This is the first one.
How are you, Kuromi?
What? Lately?
Lately.
Wait a minute, there's a lot of light coming in.
Recently?
Yes, I often see Kaede-san spilling during the tour.
I've seen you spill a lot during the tour, and I've felt it's like you.
Lately, Kuromi has been telling me too.
Please don't spill it.
She tends to spill shaved ice.
It might be dangerous next time.
Oh no.
We have to be careful.
Don't worry. Don't worry.
How are you, Rei-chan?
Lately?
Lately, yes.
I wonder... What's wrong?
I don't know... I just turned 20.
Congratulations!
I wrote on my blog that I wanted to go to a yakitori restaurant, and Hina-san called me right away.
I saw that!
Really?
She asked me when it was open.
But we've already decided on a date.
I saw it in your story.
Really?
In the story too.
How is Kaede these days?
I'm not used to saying it.
Chromin has to say it.
How are you lately, Kaede?Kaede, how are you lately?
Oh no, I've been told.
I have been lately.
Me too, but recently...
I've been getting along with Nao from Gokisei.
And Nao from Tomisato.
When I was in Okinawa for the first time...
We even talked on the phone.
What?
It's the first time I call a junior colleague.
He asked if he could call me.
I told him it's okay... because he was scared of the room.
So we stayed on the phone until he fell asleep.
It was a long call.
Here's what happened.
Here comes Mr. Tsume Odori!
And, "Yay, Mr. Tsume Odori!
Ta-da!
He said he'd like to go out to eat!
Let's eat!
Let's go!
I'm off!
Wait! Strawberry milk cream with white rice balls!
We're stuffed!
You stuffed it in there!
It's Nagoya, so I wonder if it's sweet bean paste or something.
Kintoki looks delicious too!
Kintoki! I love it! Kintoki too.
Really? It's so good!
Oshima kintoki milk cream shiratama kinako ice topped with warabimochi
Please introduce yourself.
On three.
You'll do it?
Nine, six, six.
A little backwards.
Reverse, three.Reverse, 3.
Oh, so it's a three.
Three?
Yes, you could have done it in 3.
That's right.
That's good.
I didn't notice.
Yuraku, is that what you did in the beginning?
It's always been this way.
I thought I could only do 3 with both hands.
Hey, Ray.
That's Rey.
Ray.
Ray, it's nice and easy.
What's your favorite food?
Hormones.
I told you.
I was into hormones back then.
Oranges?
I also like oranges.
Seven, I think.
Thank you very much.
From
Ta-da!
from
Thank you very much.
I don't know how to take a good picture.
This is pretty good.
If you put the trays in the right direction like this...
It's a little different.
If you drop it off the tray...
Then it'll spill.
Bon appétit.
Bon appétit!Bon appétit.
What is this?
What flavor is this?
Cream.
Kintoki.
Bon appétit.
Molasses! Delicious!
Okkun, I'm having a snack.
Okkun, he's eating a snack.
I'm pouring soybean flour on it. I'm pouring soybean flour on it.
It's so hard! Kinako...
Frog! I spilled some...
Is it okay if I spill this?
Don't worry, it won't get in.
I'm pouring it on.
I'm putting soybean flour on it.
After sprinkling soybean flour, clean it up.
I'll clean it up.
Let's eat strawberries!
Let's eat!
We will eat hiroshinago.
Yum!
How is it?
Delicious!
Strawberries and milk go well together, don't they?
Shiratama!
Mushroom flavor.
Oh...
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's okay. It's okay.
I flipped over.
That was a close one.
Congratulations on the cheese.
Maybe it's got some kind of evil spirit attached to it.
He's messing with it.
You're really messing with it.You're really messing with it.
Yeah, I am.
Oh, my God.
I can't eat this.
It's delicious.
Oh, it's pink.
Try to describe it with your hands.
Good boy.
Mochi Mochi.
I see. Mochi Mochi.
It's stickier than a trampoline.
I've had it before.
It's so good!
It's so soft.
I see the similarity.
And the shiratama is delicious too.
I'll have some too.
No? Again with the shiratama.
No, it's not.
Not even close.
After it's in your mouth
The way it disappears...
It just disappears.
Enjoy!
sweetness
Chubby
Oh, wait!
I'll use the plate.
I'll just use this one.
Delicious!
Hot, hot, hot, hot.
Good again.
It's good.
You like it?
Yeah, it's good.
Hot?Hot?
Yeah, it's hot.
That hot?
Yeah, it is.
Just because we're in California doesn't mean it's hot.
I have a cat tongue.
I finally...
In Osaka.
I did this to the makeup artist's desk.
I just...
What did you bring?
Takoyaki.
Oh, no.
That's not good.
Was it soy sauce or something?
What did you have?
What flavor?
It's changed.
Ponzu.
I'm really hungry.
I wanted to go in early to make up.
I said, "Let's bring takoyaki.
I took it.
I got a little careless when I put it down.
I spilled some.
Ume was next to me.
She took my picture.
We got into a group talk about third-term students.
Finally, this guy
He even started messing up the makeup artist's desk.
So, I got sent the talk
If I have any B news for sure
I'm going to go do B news.
That's good. That's good.
Are you writing? Are you writing it down?
Not at all.Not at all.
Maybe not at all.
It's when you throw something away that it doesn't get picked.
I know what you mean.
It's the ones that you want to talk about that don't get picked.
Okay, so if I had to pick one...
I don't know if they'll use it.
I don't know if they'll use it, but...
But you know what?
There's something that's happened in the past
With B grade news that's aired in the past.
And it's another member of the group.
What?
What is this?
I'm curious.
I don't think you'll ever know.
Well, I'm looking forward to seeing it on the air.
You're so ahead of the curve.
I don't know if they'll use it.
How did it go? Today?
I didn't think I could enjoy Nagoya so much today.
I didn't think I'd be able to enjoy Nagoya so much.
You can't enjoy Nagoya so much if you come here too often.
Just come here and go home.
It was fun, wasn't it?
It was my first time in the city.
That's for sure.
Yes, it was.
It was fun.
I hope you all have a good time.
When you come to Nagoya.
I went to two restaurants today.
You should go there.
Eat a lot!
Enjoy the concert!Enjoy the live music
Let's make summer memories!
Join us!
Subscribe to our channel and rate us highly
Please subscribe to our channel and rate us highly!
Let's go live!
We'll do our best!
Bye bye.
[ED]